[
  {
    "userInfo": {
      "fullName": "Trung Vo",
      "username": "trungvo",
      "email": "trung.vo@gmail.com",
      "phone": "6313277695",
      "role": "canvasser"
    },
    "assignments": [
      {
        "date": "10/31/2018",
        "taskName": "Task 1",
        "locations" : [
          {
            "fullAddress": "1147 N Country Rd, Stony Brook, NY 11790, USA",
            "duration": 30,
            "qaList": [
              {"question": "How are you?", "answer": "Fine thanks."},
              {"question": "Who are you?", "answer": "Trung Vo."}
            ]
          },
          {
            "fullAddress": "150 Christian Ave, Stony Brook, NY 11790, USA",
            "duration": 20,
            "qaList": [
              {"question": "How do you like this product?", "answer": "Very good."},
              {"question": "How do rate this product?", "answer": "Awesome! I would give a 5.0."}
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "date": "01/31/2018",
        "taskName": "Task 2",
        "locations" : [
          {
            "fullAddress": "100 Nicolls Rd, Stony Brook, NY 11790, USA",
            "duration": 35,
            "qaList": [
              {"question": "How are you?", "answer": "Fine thanks."},
              {"question": "Who are you?", "answer": "Trung Vo."}
            ]
          },
          {
            "fullAddress": "15 Hollow Rd, Stony Brook, NY 11790, USA",
            "duration": 45,
            "qaList": [
              {"question": "How do you like this product?", "answer": "Very good."},
              {"question": "How do rate this product?", "answer": "Awesome! I would give a 5.0."}
            ]
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    "unassignments": ["06/05/2018", "09/12/2016", "05/04/2018"]
  },
  {
    "userInfo": {
      "fullName": "Habin Park",
      "username": "habinpark",
      "email": "habin.park@gmail.com",
      "phone": "6313277695",
      "role": "canvasser"
    },
    "assignments": [
      {
        "date": "12/01/2018",
        "taskName": "Task 3",
        "locations" : [
          {
            "fullAddress": "318 Wynn Ln, Port Jefferson, NY 11777, USA",
            "duration": 10,
            "qaList": [
              {"question": "How are you?", "answer": "Fine thanks."},
              {"question": "Who are you?", "answer": "Trung Vo."}
            ]
          },
          {
            "fullAddress": "521 Lake Ave, St James, NY 11780, USA",
            "duration": 30,
            "qaList": [
              {"question": "How do you like this product?", "answer": "Very good."},
              {"question": "How do rate this product?", "answer": "Awesome! I would give a 5.0."}
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "date": "01/31/2018",
        "taskName": "Task 4",
        "locations" : [
          {
            "fullAddress": "75 Washington Pl, Stony Brook, NY 10011, USA",
            "duration": 40,
            "qaList": [
              {"question": "How are you?", "answer": "Fine thanks."},
              {"question": "Who are you?", "answer": "Trung Vo."}
            ]
          },
          {
            "fullAddress": "526 Main St, Islip, NY 11751, USA",
            "duration": 35,
            "qaList": [
              {"question": "How do you like this product?", "answer": "Very good."},
              {"question": "How do rate this product?", "answer": "Awesome! I would give a 5.0."}
            ]
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    "unassignments": ["06/05/2018", "09/12/2016", "05/04/2018"]
  }
]